Yet another SSH Tunnel Website:  [SSH Tunnel Net](https://www.ssh-tunnel.net/?utm_source=opentunnel&utm_medium=text&utm_campaign=top)

* Donate
* 

Privacy Policy
==============

At OpenTunnel.net, accessible from https://opentunnel.net, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by OpenTunnel.net and how we use it.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at [\[email protected\]](https://opentunnel.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

##### Log Files

OpenTunnel.net follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

##### Cookies and Web Beacons

Like any other website, OpenTunnel.net uses 'cookies'. These cookies are used to store information including visitors' preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users' experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors' browser type and/or other information.

##### Google DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google is one of a third-party vendor on our site. It also uses cookies, known as DART cookies, to serve ads to our site visitors based upon their visit to www.website.com and other sites on the internet. However, visitors may choose to decline the use of DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network Privacy Policy at the following URL – [https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads)

##### Third Pary Privacy Policies

OpenTunnel.net's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites. What Are Cookies?

##### Online Privacy Policy Only

This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in OpenTunnel.net. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

##### Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.

OpenTunnel.net
==============

OpenTunnel.net provides free tunneling services since 2021. Our mission is "Internet Freedom", which means there are no restrictions on accessing any content on the Internet with a reliable connection.

© 2021 - 2024 [opentunnel.net](https://opentunnel.net/) | [Terms of Service](https://opentunnel.net/term-of-service) | [Privacy Policy](https://opentunnel.net/privacy-policy)

##### Thank you for helping to develop OpenTunnel.net

OpenTunnel.net always provide free service at full speed and always maintained servers. We provide servers with various locations around the world for free and will continue to grow where possible. Your donation helps us rent servers and make this site better than others.

#####  Bitcoin

#####  Ethereum

#####  Monero

#####  Litecoin

 just now

##### This site uses cookies

**OpenTunnel.net and our partners** use cookies and similar technology to collect and analyse information about the users of this website.  
We use this information to enhance the content, advertising and other services available on the site.

Agree
